A Cookie Cutter Christmas is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by Christie Will Wolf.
Two longtime rivals and elementary school teachers duke it out during the holidays in a Christmas cookie
bake-off, but their real feud ignites over a shared interest in a handsome single dad.
With both determined to win the prize and the romance, their competitiveness
could jeopardize what matters most this Christmas season.
Christie Reynolds, played by Erin Krakow.
Chef Krueger, played by Alan Thicke.
James, played by David Haydn-Jones.
Penny Miller, played by Miranda Frigon.
Bev Reynolds, played by Laura Soltis.
Lily, played by Genea Charpentier.
Our Little Secret is a 2024 American christmas romantic comedy film
directed by Stephen Herek and written by Hailey DeDominicis.
It stars Lindsay Lohan, alongside an ensemble cast featuring Ian Harding, Tim Meadows, Jon
Rudnitsky, Judy Reyes, Henry Czerny, Chris Parnell, and Kristin Chenoweth.
The film was a part of Lohan's creative partnership with Netflix,
under which she also executive produced the project.
Our Little Secret follows Avery (Lohan), who is spending her first Christmas with her boyfriend's family but
discovers her ex is also part of the holiday festivities and decides to hide their romantic history.
Production began in Atlanta, in January 2024, and
concluded late in the following month.
The film was released on Netflix, on November 27, 2024.
It received mixed reviews from critics and debuted at number one on the streaming
service's most watched films list, where it stayed for two weeks.
The film explores themes of romance, woman director, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.